Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge, the top idol group Iron Frill came to our town!
They'll be packing seats with fans for sure!
I still can't believe we were picked to be their opening act at Saga Arena!
Kotaro isn't taking chances and is keeping Ai from performing,
so no one recognizes her as Iron Frill's original leader!
Meanwhile, Ai's been doing solo gigs while we prepare for the concert.
Frontier Street feels weird without her.
We can't mess up again like we did at the EFS! The anxiety is real!
To make matters worse, Iron Frill's new leader, Shiori, tried to get Ai to join their group!
We won't let that happen, no matter what!
Listen up, number three. You should join Iron Frill.
Everything's just fine. Ai is not going to abandon us,
and she's not gonna join those girls in Iron Frill.
I mean, aside from the whole being a zombie thing, she's a part of our group.
One of us.
I sure hope you're right about that.
If she were here, she'd probably yell at me for being so nervous about the show.
No kidding! I would be in full-on rage mode about it.
She's like,
I don't want to hear that kind of talk. Stop worrying and zombie up!
We shouldn't tell the other girls about what we just saw. It would only worry them.
After all, the Saga Arena show is coming up fast.
And we're gonna rock it!
We're gonna rock it!
We'll rock it!